{
    "id": "ffb954d4823c4ce680fdec1174888d6d",
    "title": "State verbs exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "2bf4da6040564fb0aeb00d1941bebd6f",
            "title": "State Verbs Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I ………………… this flavor.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "like",
                        "am liking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………. fine.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "am feeling",
                        "feel",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………. your dad tomorrow.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "see",
                        "am seeing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I called her because I ……………….. to talk.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "needed",
                        "was needing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………….. that he is innocent.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "believe",
                        "am believing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………….. his motives.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "doubt",
                        "am doubting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ……………….. what you mean.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "see",
                        "am seeing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ……………… her immediately.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "recognized",
                        "was recognizing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The meat ………………. bad.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "smells",
                        "is smelling"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He …………………. 72 kilos.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "weighs",
                        "is weighing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}